var questions = [
  {
    qprompt: "How many Pokémon were in the first game?",
    c1: "A) 100",
    c2: "B) 151",
    c3: "C) 150",
    c4: "D) 101",
    answer: "B) 151",
    answered: false,
  },
  {
    qprompt: "When was Pokémon FIRST released?",
    c1: "A) 1996",
    c2: "B) 1997",
    c3: "C) 1998",
    c4: "D) 1999",
    answer: "A) 1996",
    answered: false,
  },
  {
    qprompt: "Can Pikachu learn Surf?",
    c1: "A) Yes",
    c2: "B) No",
    c3: "C) No but he can when he evolves",
    c4: "D) Yes but he can only use it in combat",
    answer: "B) No",
    answered: false,
  },
  {
    qprompt: "How can (specific) Pokémon change gender?",
    c1: "A)Super Hidden Easter Eggs",
    c2: "B) Evolving",
    c3: "C) Trading",
    c4: "D) Never happens",
    answer: "B) Evolving",
    answered: false,
  },
  {
    qprompt:
      "Which Pokémon has the highest base stat total (Adding up all the stats from HP to Speed) ?",
    c1: "A) Mega Rayquaza",
    c2: "B) Mega Mewtwo X",
    c3: "C) Mega Mewtwo Y",
    c4: "D) All of the above",
    answer: "D) All of the above",
    answered: false,
  },
  {
    qprompt:
      "Which trait affects your Pokémon's stats PERMANENTLY (Before Battle) ?",
    c1: "A) Beauty",
    c2: "B) Abilities",
    c3: "C) Nature",
    c4: "D) No such trait",
    answer: "C) Nature",
    answered: false,
  },
  {
    qprompt: "What are IVs?",
    c1: "A) Injected Values", //what the police check for when they stop you
    c2: "B) Individual Values",
    c3: "C) Indeterminant Values",
    c4: "D) Don't Exist",
    answer: "B) Individual Values",
    answered: false,
  },
  {
    qprompt: "What are EVs?",
    c1: "A) Effort Values",
    c2: "B) Energy Values",
    c3: "C) Entertaining Values",
    c4: "D) 1999",
    answer: "A) Effort Values",
    answered: false,
  },
  {
    qprompt: "Who controls the majority of the Pokémon ranking and tiers?",
    c1: "A) Nintendo",
    c2: "B) Game Freak",
    c3: "C) SMOGON",
    c4: "D) DOSUKE",
    answer: "C) SMOGON",
    answered: false,
  },
  {
    qprompt:
      "Which non-legendary Pokémon got banned FIRST from OU, the most popular format?",
    c1: "A) Garchomp",
    c2: "B) Wobbuffet",
    c3: "C) Salamence",
    c4: "D) Kangaskhan",
    answer: "B) Wobbuffet",
    answered: false,
  },
  {
    qprompt:
      "Which Pokémon FIRST OUTCLASSED its evolution (in terms of the tiers) ?",
    c1: "A) Chansey",
    c2: "B) Porygon",
    c3: "C) Dusclops",
    c4: "D) None of the above",
    answer: "C) Dusclops",
    answered: false,
  },
  {
    qprompt: "What is the most controversial mechanic in Pokémon?", //This is kinda an opinion question. Billy- Well yes but actually no because only one of these mechanics got banned.
    c1: "A) Hazards(Stealth Rock)",
    c2: "B) Trapping(Shadow Tag and Arena Trap)",
    c3: "C) Switching",
    c4: "D) Pokemon is above controversy",
    answer: "B) Trapping(Shadow Tag and Arena Trap)",
    answered: false,
  },
  {
    qprompt: "How many IVs can exist in a single stat?",
    c1: "A) 23",
    c2: "B) 31",
    c3: "C) 256",
    c4: "D) 510",
    answer: "B) 31",
    answered: false,
  },
  {
    qprompt: "How many total EVs can you have on a Pokémon?",
    c1: "A) 23",
    c2: "B) 31",
    c3: "C) 256",
    c4: "D) 510",
    answer: "D) 510",
    answered: false,
  },
  {
    qprompt:
      "How many EVs can be converted to actual stats, assuming your Pokémon is LVL 100?",
    c1: "A) 507",
    c2: "B) 508",
    c3: "C) 509",
    c4: "D) 510",
    answer: "B) 508",
    answered: false,
  },
  {
    qprompt: "Do DVs exist?",
    c1: "A) Yes",
    c2: "B) No",
    c3: "C) Yes but only in fan games",
    c4: "D) Yes but only in gen 1 and 2",
    answer: "D) Yes but only in gen 1 and 2",
    answered: false,
  },
];
export { questions };
